

<html>
<body>

<item>
        <description>Reputation is everything in a world of icons and popularity contests. So why not score some points here and there by being the nice guy? This is the way Kang Shin-gi legitimizes the fake personality he has everyone believing. Armed with his above average looks and a (completely false) angel-like personality, he has every girl in school head over heels, and all the guys looking to him for guidance. With the exception of having a screwed up cross-dressing devil for a dad, Shin-gi’s life is absolute perfection (*cough* of lies), until one day, Um Seung-hui transfers to his school.

While being a complete martial artist freak, she also likes to fib just a little in front of those who know her… you know, like acting like shes just a scared little girl whod play with kittens rather than break brick walls with her head! After all, how can anything go wrong when youre as cute as Seung-hui?

Fate has brought these two masters of lies together, and the two must battle it out to see who will be crowned the 
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/2.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/Zippy-Ziggy</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>Bi-Kwang and Hwa-Rin try in vain to shake ---Sang Pil Gold Cobra Jin and his men, but ultimately they are forced to defend themselves. Unfortunately, Bi-Kwang and Hwa-Rin lose, and the Sword of the Flowers is taken from them. Bi-Kwang and Hwa-Rin regroup, pursuing Sang Pil Jin in an effort to retrieve the sword-but then Sang Pil and his men learn that Bi-Kwang and Hwa-Rin arent the only ones after them. Sang Pils superior, Master Yoo, has learned that Sang Pil planned to keep the sword for himself, and has approached Shi-Yun, leader of the Black Serpents, for help.

The lives of Bi-Kwang, Hwa-Rin, Sang Pil Jin, and his men are all in danger, as Master Yoo and the Black Serpents join forces and search for the sword together.
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/3.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/The-Ruler-Of-The-Land</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>Two prisoners managed to escape after the police truck carrying them crashed on the highway. One of them , Mr Sawazaki (?) is a gangster who has sent 10 opposite bosses to hospital. The other called You - our protagonist - is a con artist whose cheating profile has piled up to approximately 100 billion yen. Accidentally, You then becomes the new teacher for the nearby high school, under the new name Takeda Shindo, and according to a deal of Hammer Session with the headmaster.
The story is about a teacher who has a past record as a con-artist. It has its own unique taste, which makes it distinctive from other series about teachers, such as GTO and Gokusen. 
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/4.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/Hammer-Session</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>This is a spin-off story of the manga GTO(Great Teacher Onizuka). This takes place directly after the Teshigawara arc[after he was shot by him]
After Eikichi Onizuka was shot by the former teacher Teshigara, he was sent to the hospital. Shortly afterwards he escape... 
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/5.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/GTO-Shonan-14-Days</path>
</item>

<item>
        <description>Twelve years before the events at the focus of the series, the nine-tailed demon fox attacked Konohagakure. It was a powerful demon fox; a single swing of one of its nine tails would raise tsunamis and flatten mountains. It raised chaos and slaughtered many people, until the leader of the Leaf Village - the Fourth Hokage - defeated it by sacrificing his own life to seal the demon inside a newly-born child. That child's name was Naruto Uzumaki.
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/12.jpg"/>
        </description>
  <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/Naruto</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>Greatness, Glory, Gold. A Pirate Named Gold Roger also known as the Pirate King has conquered this all. He was executed with an unknown reason but before he died he had revealed his last word about The legendary Treasure named One Piece which was hidden in the Grand Line. 22 years after his Death, A Pirate named Monkey D. Luffy appeared and has only one Goal, To Become the Next Pirate King and Find The Treasure One Piece. This Start The Never Ending Adventure. Monkey D. Luffy, inspired by his childhood hero Red-Haired Shanks, sets out on a journey to find the legendary treasure One Piece, to become the new Pirate King, and after eating the devil's fruit gains the power to do so. To accomplish this, he must reach the end of the most deadly and dangerous ocean: The Grand Line. But first he must find a crew.

During the course of the story, the crew contend with both other less moral pirate crews and the Marines. The latter are the subordinates of the World Government, who seek justice by ending the Golden Age of Pirates. Many background story elements involve the delicate balance of power between the World Government and the world's most powerful pirate crews. Also, the Craziest Crew in the world .
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/13.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/One-Piece</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>Ichigo Kurosaki has always been able to see ghosts, but this ability doesn't change his life nearly as much as his close encounter with Rukia Kuchiki, a soul reaper and member of the mysterious Soul Society. While fighting a hollow, an evil spirit that preys on humans who display spiritual energy, Rukia attempts to lend Ichigo some of her powers so that he can save his family; but much to her surprise, Ichigo absorbs every last drop of her energy. Now a full-fledged soul reaper himself, Ichigo quickly learns that the world he inhabits is one full of dangerous spirits and, along with Rukia, it's Ichigo's job to protect the innocent from hollows and help the spirits themselves find peace. In 2005, Bleach was awarded the Shogakukan Manga Award in the shounen category.
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/14.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/Bleach</path>
</item>
<item>
        <description>Katori Itto and Yura Kazuma are childhood rivals. Itto is small and quarrelsome while Kazuma is big and vindictive. Itto has been holding a grudge against Kazuma for a long time from the scar Kazuma made him five years ago during a fight… After years of travelling with his father, Itto finally returns to Japan only to reunite with a childhood rival, Kazuma. A very hilarious combination of circumstances will bring the unpredictable Itto to join Kazumas soccer team at Seiga Middle School… The manga follows this wacky duo as they, alongside the rest of the team, battle other middle school teams on the road to becoming Japan s best. The intense footy goodness is only second to the ridiculously hilarious situations that Itto somehow manages to find himself in.
                <img src="http://app-truyentranh.googlecode.com/svn/img/15.jpg"/>
        </description>
        <path>http://kissmanga.com/Manga/Kattobi-Itto</path>
</item>
</body>
</html>
